







PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

With the background of a System Engineer, Kay Kim is a highly motivated web developer with complete understanding of software engineering principles. He specializes in web development using latest technologies such as React, Redux, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, bootstrap and JQuery. His recent projects consist of creating Ticket Management System that use React & Redux, Javascript, PHP, and Google Map API



EXPERTISE

- React
 - Redux
- PHP
- Laravel
- Javascript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- **JQuery**
- MySQL
- **Nodeis**
- Java
- Ajax



Git

Github

Express

Microsoft Access

MongoDB

Wireless



CERTIFICATION

- CCNA (Cisco Certified Network Associate)
- CCNP (Switch/Router)
- Networking operating system
- ICE (Information communication Engineer)



EDUCATION

2017-2018

Advance Programming, Full Stack Developer

Rutgers University Coding CE Courses

2014-2017

Programming and System

LaGuardia Community College Associate Degree



WORK EXPERIENCE

2018-Present

Web Developer

Threeon Inc

- Developing a Data Communication System by React & Redux, JavaScript, HTML5, Mysgl and Laravel Framework
- Creating Service Map area by Google Map API
- Designing Ticket Management System UI
- Developing ERP System Data import & export by Javascript, Laravel, and Mysql
- Maintaining Client's website functionality by Javascript

2016-2018

IT specialist, System Engineer

KeySolution Provider Inc

- Maintaining website and applications, including contents updates and testing
- Operating system and management tools for clients such as Samsung, Hansol, and ZT group INC, Installing software
- Constituting network environment, installing server and Ipphones
- Updating company's security program fetches and checking system's status with SQL query

2012-2014

Assistant IT specialist

Sky wireless, Inc

- Repaired computers and mobile devices' hardware with OEM parts and diagnosed devices software issue with its pre-installed software.
- Configuring Client's Cisco switch device firewall setting
- Installed and maintains wired, and wireless(IP) security cameras, computers and other devices
- Managed and provided technical support for clients in timely and effective manner